Guide to the New Dramatists Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Administrative Files, 1949-1996; Series II; 114.58; (100 boxes) + 12 broadside folders
  - Financial Records
    - Applications
      - Borkhuis, Charles, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Broadhurst, Kent, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Brody, Alan, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Brown, Carlyle, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Busa, Steve, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Caliban, Richard, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Calman, Craig, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Camp, Judson, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Campbell, Michael, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Carter, Lonnie, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Caruso, Rosemarie, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Clark, Kathleen, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Cohen, Alice Eve, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Conger, Trista, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Curran, Keith, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Conrad, Hy, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Criscione, Elaine, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Curzon, Daniel, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Danese, Joshua, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Dinwiddie, Michael, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Dishman, Madge, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Duff, Michael, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Egloff, Elizabeth, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Eisman, Mark, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Eliet, David, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Faigao-Hall, Linda, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Farley, Edward, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Ferrero, Chuck, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Formichella, Elise, 1988 (Box 104)
      - France, Juliann, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Francis, Veronica, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Fries, Kenny, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Gale, Zona, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Garrett, Lillian, 1988 (Box 104)
      - GeBauer, Judy, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Georgans, Barbara, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Graff, Stephen, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Graham, Barbara, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Gunderson, Joanna, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Hagedorn, Jeff, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Hansen, Jim, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Hardison, David, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Harrell, Leslie, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Harta, Vincent, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Hatcher, Jeffrey, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Hawkins, Cheryl, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Heefner, David, 1988 (Box 104)
      - Higgins, Joanna, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Himelsbach, James, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Hinton, Tom, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Houghton, Katherine, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Howie, Diana M., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Huber, Kathleen, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Humphrey, Olga, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Hutzler, Laurie H., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Jensen, Julie, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Johnson, Charles R., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Jones, Christopher, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Jones, Thomas C., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Joselovitz, Ernest A., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Kassin, Michael, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Kaufman, Lynne, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Keating, Bernie, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Kelleher, James N., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Kelly, Kevin, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Kilburn, Aileen, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Klayman, Jeff, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Klein, Jon, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Kraar, Adam, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Kramer, Frederick, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Koch, Joanne, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Krauss, Kenneth, 1988 (Box 105)
      - La Farge, W. E. R., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Lanci, Gabriel, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Lewis, Carter, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Lizardi, Joseph, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Long, Charles C., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Lopez, Eduardo Ivan, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Lovell, Glenville, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Lukeman, Brenda Shoshanna, 1988 (Box 105)
      - MacAdam, Will, 1988 (Box 105)
      - McCarter, Orville, 1988 (Box 105)
      - McClary, Thomas A., 1988 (Box 105)
      - McGravie, Annie, 1988 (Box 105)
      - McGuire, Michael, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Malik, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Mark, David, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Masterson, Kelly, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Matheny, Charles, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Mattair, Mims, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Meredith, Kevin, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Mohat, Marvel, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Moore, Thomas, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Morris, Sandra, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Mroczka, Paul, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Muschell, David, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Nielson, Brenda, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Noll, Robert Thomas, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Olson, Donald, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Pardi, Robert J., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Parry, Roberta, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Patricca, Nicholas, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Pazillo, Joseph J., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Pepper, Cary, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Phelan, A. S., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Phillips, Mary Bracken, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Pizzato, Mark, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Pringle, P. J., undated (Box 105)
      - Pryor, Debbie, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Radavich, David, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Rael, Elisa, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Rand, George I., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Rand, Harry, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Ravenal, Cornelia, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Reich, Brian, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Renderer, Scott, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Reynolds, Lillian, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Rosenau, Anita H., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Ross, Douglass, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Roth, S. J., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Sater, Steven, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Schein, David, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Schewe, Phillip F., 1988 (Box 105)
      - Schoelwer, Edward, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Serena, Ellie, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Sjorgen, Craig, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Skolnick, Zan, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Slanton, Gram, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Smith-Dawson, Beverly, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Snave, E (Evans Production), 1988 (Box 105)
      - Sorbello, Donna, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Sterrett, Jean, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Steward, Richard, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Stolzer, Alan, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Stone, Forrest, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Sulsona, Mike, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Swansen, Larry, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Tammany, Susan, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Taav, Michael, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Tavel, Ronald, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Timm, Frederick, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Torres, Sandra, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Turner, Jeffrey Howard, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Vago, Sandra Marie, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Vincent, Paul, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Vosburgh, Susan, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Wadud, Ali, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Ware, Elliott Anthony, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Waxberg, Charles, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Weitzner, Kobi, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Werboff, Paula, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Williams, John-Michael Young Bear, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Witten, Matthew, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Wolpe, David, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Worsley, Dale, 1988 (Box 105)
      - Zuk, Tom, 1988 (Box 105)
    - Activities reports, undated (Box 105)
    - Financial statements and applications, undated (Box 105)
    - Pamphlets and photograph, undated (Box 105)
    - O'Harra, undated (Box 105)
    - Craft discussions, 1957-1958 (Box 105)
    - Member's guide, undated (Box 105)
    - "Marvelous Times" by Brown, Michael, 1988 (Box 105)
    - Printed material and correspondence, 1980 (Box 105)
    - York, Y., undated (Box 106)
    - "Love-Shorts" by Tudisco, Joseph, undated (Box 106)
    - Corrigan, Pat, undated (Box 106)
    - Rosen, Sheldon, undated (Box 106)
    - Nagy, Phyllis, undated (Box 106)
    - Alvarez, Lynne, undated (Box 106)
    - Childs, Casey, undated (Box 106)
    - Bosakowski, Phil, undated (Box 106)
    - Applications, 1987 (Box 106)
    - Contact information cards, undated; 6 (Box 106)
    - Activities, 1949-1958; 18 (Box 107)
    - Activities, 1959-1961; 15 (Box 108)
    - Activities, 1962-1969 (Box 109)
    - Activities, 1970-1972; 13 (Box 110)
    - Activities, 1973-1989; 16 (Box 111)
    - Luncheon lists, 1971 (Box 112)
    - Miscellaneous financial papers, 1971 (Box 112)
    - Theatre admissions, 1971-1972 (Box 112)
    - Industry drives and luncheons, 1972-1977; 14 (Box 112)
    - Industry drives and luncheons, 1981-1987; 14 (Box 113)
    - Lazarus fund, 1987-1988; 3 (Box 113)
    - Playbill magazine, 1949-1963 (Box 114)
    - Playbill magazine, 1960-1980 (Box 115)
    - Letter from Crouse, Russel, undated (Box 116)
    - Letter from Roosevelt, Eleanor, 1961 (Box 116)
    - Letters from Marx, Groucho, 1969 (Box 116)
    - A talk on playwriting by Lindsay, Howard, 1942 (Box 116)
    - Incoming correspondence for O'Harra, Michaela, 1951-1953 (Box 116)
    - Testimonial correspondence, 1949-1969 (Box 116)
    - Original papers for exhibit, 1949-1961 (Box 116)
    - Letter from Inge, William, 1966 (Box 116)
    - "The Amen Corner" by Baldwin, James (2 copies), undated (Box 116)
    - Letters to John Golden, 1940-1950 (Box 116)
    - Sidney Lumet testimonial, 1969 (Box 116)
    - Proposed plans, 1957-1958 (Box 116)
    - Celebrity doodle auction, 1987 (Box 116)
    - Elia Kazan craft discussion - transcript, 1955 November 7 (Box 116)
    - Howard Lindsay craft discussion - transcript, 1956 January 12 (Box 116)
    - Arthur Miller craft discussion - transcript, 1956 February 27 (Box 116)
    - "A History and Evaluation of the New Dramatists Committee"; dissertation by Howard Vincent Burman, 1971; 2 (Box 116)
    - Brief programs descriptions, undated (Box 116)
    - Scrapbooks, undated; 2 (Box 116)
    - Donor cards, undated (Box 117)
    - Photographs, undated; 6 (Box 117)
    - Contact sheets, 1978-1987; 9 (Box 118)
    - Mailing lists/ labels, undated (Box 118)
    - Mailing lists, undated; 4 (Box 118)
    - Celebrity doodles
      - Orbach, Jerry, undated (Box 119)
      - Asner, Ed, 1984 (Box 119)
      - Wallach, Eli, undated (Box 119)
      - Havoc, June, 1969 April 25 (Box 119)
      - Tiegs, Cheryl, undated (Box 119)
      - Piggot-Smith, Tim, undated (Box 119)
      - Harris, Ed, 1990 September 11 (Box 119)
      - Ferrer, Jose, 1988 (Box 119)
      - Tyzach, Margaret, undated (Box 119)
      - Raphael, Sally Jessy, 1990 November 3 (Box 119)
      - Mazursky, Paul, 1991 (Box 119)
      - Fitzgerald, Geraldine, undated (Box 119)
      - Henley, Beth, 1992 (Box 119)
      - Klugman, Jack, undated (Box 119)
      - Plimpton, George, 1991 (Box 119)
      - Powell, Jane, 1991 (Box 119)
      - Lemmon, Jack, undated (Box 119)
      - Copeland, Joan, 1991 (Box 119)
      - Curtin, Jane, undated (Box 119)
      - Nichols, Peter, undated (Box 119)
      - Weaver, Fritz, 1988 (Box 119)
      - Rowlands, Gena, 1990 (Box 119)
      - Vaccaro, Brenda, undated (Box 119)
      - Gifford, Kathie Lee, 1988 (Box 119)
      - Gifford, Frank, undated (Box 119)
      - Sahl, Mort, undated (Box 119)
      - Zimbalist, Stephanie, undated (Box 119)
      - Collins, Judy, undated (Box 119)
      - Shields, Brooke, undated (Box 119)
      - Shanley, John Patrick, undated (Box 119)
      - Adams, Mason, undated (Box 119)
      - Randall, Tony, undated (Box 119)
      - Matthau, Walter, 1971 (Box 119)
      - Hasen, Irwin (framed), 1981 (Box 120 (Oversize))
      - Howes, Sally Ann (framed), 1983 (Box 120 (Oversize))
      - von Furstenberg, Betsy, undated (Box 121 (Oversize))
      - Minnelli, Liza and Rivera, Chita, 1984 (Box 121 (Oversize))
      - Loudon, Dorothy, 1984 (Box 121 (Oversize))
      - Lawrence, Carol and Kert, Larry, undated (Box 121 (Oversize))
      - Moody, Ron, 1984 (Box 121 (Oversize))
      - Jacobi, 1961 (Box 121 (Oversize))
    - Luncheon journal mechanicals, 1986 (Box 121 (Oversize))
    - Playbill mechanicals, undated (Box 121 (Oversize))
    - "Readings" mechanicals, 1981 Fall (Box 121 (Oversize))
    - Other mechanicals, 1982 (Box 121 (Oversize))
    - 40th Anniversary postcard mechanicals, 1989 (Box 121 (Oversize))
    - Mechanicals for luncheons advertisements, undated; 4 (Box 122 (Oversize))
    - Newsletter mechanicals, undated; 2 (Box 123 (Oversize))
    - Luncheon program mechanicals, 1986 (Box 123 (Oversize))
    - Luncheon program mechanicals, 1980-1989; 5 (Box 124 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbook, 1960-1968 (Box 125 (Oversize))
    - Scrapbooks, 1961-1973; 2 (Box 126 (Oversize))
    - "Readings" mechanicals, 1985 (Box 127 (Oversize))
    - Restricted material, undated (Box 128)
      Restricted until 2050. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
    - Audiovisual Material
      Box 129, 131, and 132 contain audiovisual material. Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult access services for further information.
      - New Dramatists Committee, Playwrights Lecture Series (sound recordings)
        Box 129 contains audiotape reels and audio belts (Dictabelt). Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
        - Stark Young, Morasco, 1959 May 7; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244427)
        - Abe Burrows, Morosco Theatre, 1959 May 21; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244435)
        - F. Curtis Canfield, Phoenix Theatre, 1959 October 23; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244443)
          Contents are included below.
          "The Hostage", Brendan Behan
          Refer Juno
          Irish plays lack [?], Plot of Hostage
          Walpurgisnacht (Wagner)
          Behan writes in tradition of Irish theatre
          1899: Formation of theatre
          Summation: What each Contributed
          This his Apothesis
          11 [?] [?] now
          French influence
          language
          old + new
        - Louis Kronenberger, "The Restoraton", Ploenix Theatre, 1959 November 5; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244450)
        - Whitehead?, Golden Theatre, late 1959 or early 1960?; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244468)
        - Michel Saint-Denis, Morasco Theatre, 1959 November 19; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244476)
        - "Passion" / "Ghost Dance" [?], 1972 June 7-10, 1973 May 15-19; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244484)
          7.5 ips
        - Jeffrey Jones, "Postcard" #1, 1984 January 19; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244492)
        - J. Silver / New Year's / New Year's / Traffic, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244500)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244518)
        - Donald Wollner, "Sky Blue Pink", undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244526)
        - "Ring Around the Rosy" / "A Deck" (all cues), Willowtrack Audio, NY, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244534)
          7.5 ips, 1/4 track, mono, contains cues 1 through 10
        - "Ring Around the Rosy", Creaking, Willowtrack Audio, NY, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244542)
          7.5 ips, 1/4 track, mono
        - #1 Exposed, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244559)
          2-track
        - Moss Hart - Stan Chervin, Act I, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244567)
        - John Shanley, "Women of Manhattan", 1985 April 24; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244575)
        - State of the Union, 1985 January 23; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244583)
        - Shirley Hillard, "The Mole", 1985 April 15; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244591)
        - Steinbach, "My Life in Art", 1986 May 6; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244609)
        - John Pielmeier, "Haunted Lives", 1984 February 28; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244617)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244625)
        - Mac Wellman, "The Nain Rouge" / "The Distance to the Moon", 1986 January 21; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244633)
        - Bouchard, "Pelopia's Doll", 1986 April 21; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244641)
        - Chess, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244658)
        - Laura Harrington, "Free Fall", 1985 March 6; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244666)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244674)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244682)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244690)
        - Stephen Levi, "Bombs on the Half-Shell", 1984 October 4; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244708)
        - Crowd Noises, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244716)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244724)
        - Porter, Sondheim, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244732)
        - Figaro, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244740)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244757)
        - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244765)
        - Stark Young (Dictaphone belt), 1959 May 7; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244781)
        - Abe Burrows (Dictaphone belt), 1959 May 21; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244773)
        - F. Curtis Canfield (Dictaphone belt), 1959 October 23; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244807)
        - Robert Whitehead (Dictaphone belt), undated; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244799)
        - Michel Saint Denis (Dictaphone belt), 1959 November 19; 1 (Box 129, Item barcode 39002091244815)
      - "Edited Harem, 15 minutes", YCALMSS690; 1; videoreels (Box 131, Item barcode 39002102370195)
        Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
        This item has been digitized.
      - "Jay", Anthony Giardina, 1984 February 27; 1 (Box 131, Item barcode 39002091244823)
      - "Mortally Fine", Bill Sibley, 1984 February 15; 1 (Box 131, Item barcode 39002091244831)
      - "End of Radio" - Act I, Sherry Kramer, 1985 May 30; 1 (Box 131, Item barcode 39002091244849)
      - Theme from "A Summer Place", undated; 1 (Box 131, Item barcode 39002091244856)
      - Open Exec Comm, 1986 June 2; 1; 01:29:00; A high amount of background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. Static can be heard on the tape. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244864)
        Audiovisual material. Restricted fragile. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
      - Board Exec, undated; 1; 00:40:05; The program begins and ends abruptly. High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244872)
      - Full Board Meeting, Paul Weiss, 1986 January 22; 1; 01:49:42; The program begins and ends abruptly. High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244880)
      - Bd Exec Mtg, 1984 November 27; 1; 01:30:56; A high amount of hum can be heard. The program is very distorted at times. A high amount of buzz can be heard. The program is unintelligible at times. The program ends abruptly. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244898)
      - Brd Exec Comm Mtg, December 14; 1; 01:02:28; The program begins and ends abruptly. Static can be heard on the tape. There is high background noise on the tape. The program is distorted at times. Audio on the right channel was recorded at a lower level. Audio on the right channel is silent from 39:36-40:48. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244906)
      - Full Bd Mtg., 1986 April 9; 1; 01:41:28; High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program begins abruptly. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244914)
      - Exec Board Comm, 1986 January 20; 1; 01:48:53; The program begins and ends abruptly. High background noise can be heard. The program is distorted at times. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244922)
      - George Abbott Luncheon, pre-dinner speakers, 1986 May 16; 1; 00:33:57; The program begins abruptly. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244930)
      - Long-range Plan Mtg., 1984 March 21; 1; This audiocassette is blank. It has not been digitized. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244948)
      - Full Board mtg. - board + writers, 1984 January 18; 1; 01:34:28; The program begins and ends abruptly. The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244955)
      - Bd Exec. Comm Mtg. / Writers Exec, cassette #2, 1984 January 16; 1; 01:31:15; The program begins and ends abruptly. The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244963)
      - Full Board Meeting, 1985 May 9; 1; 00:46:54; The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244971)
      - Board Exec Comm, 1984 February 8; 1; 01:26:56; The program begins and ends abruptly. The program is distorted at times. High background noise can be heard on the tape. Audio on the right channel was recorded at a lower level. Audio on the right channel gradually decreases in volume over the last 40 minutes. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244989)
      - Bd Exec, cassette #1, 1984 March 7; 1; 01:34:40; The program begins and ends abruptly. High background noise can be heard on the tape. Audio on the right channel was recorded at a lower level. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091244997)
      - Bd Exec Mtg., cassette #1, 1984 March 7; 1; 00:11:24; The program begins abruptly. High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245002)
      - Bd meeting, New Dramatists, October 22; 1; 00:54:42; High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program begins and ends abruptly. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245010)
      - Bd meeting, January 18; 1; 01:00:36; High background noise can be heard on the tape. Static is also on the tape. A high amount of hiss can be heard. The program was recorded at a very low level at times. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245028)
      - Full Board mtg @ Paul Weiss, 1984 March 14; 1; 01:03:09; The program is distorted at times. Audio in the right channel was recorded at a lower level. High background noise can be heard on the tape. The volume decreases gradually over the course of the last 18 minutes. A high amount of hiss can also be heard over the last 18 minutes. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245036)
      - Board Exec Mtg, cassette #1, 1984 April 4; 1; 01:33:49; The program begins and ends abruptly. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245044)
      - Board Exec Comm. Mtg., 1983 January 11; 1; 01:33:55; The program begins and ends abruptly. High background noise can be heard on the tape. The audio is sometimes unclear or sounds hollow. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245051)
      - Exec Comm Mtg., 1985 December 2; 1; 01:41:17; The program begins and ends abruptly. High background noise can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245069)
      - Bd mtg, October 22; 1; 01:02:42; High background noise can be heard. The program is distorted at times. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245077)
      - Board Exec, 1982 September 6; 1; 01:29:36; A high amount of hum can be heard. A high amount of buzz is on the tape. The program is very distorted at times. The program is unintelligible. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245085)
      - Bd Exec Comm, 1984 October 30; 1; 01:31:41; The program begins and ends abruptly. Static can be heard on the tape. The program is distorted at times. High amounts of hum and buzz are on the tape. High background noise can be heard. (Box 132, Item barcode 39002091245093)
    - Watts, "Calypso", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245531)
    - "Calypso", To be Recorded, Chopin #1 Concrete, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245549)
    - "Figaro", "Romeo + Juliet", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245556)
    - Noel Coward, Sym. #3, "Nutcracker" excerpts, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245564)
    - "La Triata", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245572)
    - Pagliacci, Anderson 3, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245580)
    - Prologue, "Shame", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245598)
      7.5 ips, track 1
    - Recorded, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245606)
    - "44 on 44th", 1984 January 19; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245614)
    - "Aida", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245622)
    - Untitled, undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245648)
    - "Go to Heaven", undated; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245655)
    - Jacques Charon, Golden Theatre ?, 1960 March 10; 1 (Box 130, Item barcode 39002091245663)